{
  "shortDescription": "Test your knowledge of YOYO tricks and history.",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "What is a YOYO?",
      "answers": ["Toy", "Game", "Food"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Where did YOYO originate?",
      "answers": ["Greece", "China", "USA"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a 'Sleeper'?",
      "answers": ["Trick", "Toy", "Player"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is 'YOYO Ma'?",
      "answers": ["Cellist", "YOYOer", "Inventor"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a 'Loop'?",
      "answers": ["Trick", "String", "Toy"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 'Walk the Dog'?",
      "answers": ["Trick", "Game", "Toy"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a 'String'?",
      "answers": ["Part", "Toy", "Game"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 'Around the World'?",
      "answers": ["Trick", "Game", "Toy"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who invented YOYO?",
      "answers": ["Flores", "Nakamoto", "Einstein"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 'YOYO Day'?",
      "answers": ["June6", "May5", "July4"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Have you followed @watchcoin?",
      "answers": ["Yes", "No", "Soon"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 2
    }
  ]
}
